const data = [
  {
    question:
      "What mountain is visible from the West Seattle Bridge on a clear day?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Mount Everest", "Broken Top", "Mount Kilimanjaro"],
    correctAnswer: "Mount Rainier",
  },

  {
    question:
      "There's a troll in Seattle!  He's huge and hides under a bridge in what part of town?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Renton", "White Center", "Capitol Hill"],
    correctAnswer: "Fremont",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Seattle has bridges, lol!  But it's famous for having the longest of this type of bridge:",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The longest double-decker bridge in America",
      "The world's tallest bridge",
      "The shortest bridge in America",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The world's longest floating bridge",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Seattle has art museums of course, and it's home to this not-so-nicely named one: ",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The Go-Away Museum",
      "The Museum of Useless Clothes",
      "The Mueseum of Bad Drivers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Museum of Bad Art",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Despite being one of the rainiest cites in country, Seattlites buy more of this item than any other city in America:",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Bathing suits", "Snow shoes", "Sunscreen"],
    correctAnswer: "Sunglasses",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Pickleball, one of the fastest growing sports around the world, began in 1965 on this island near Seattle:",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Whidbey Island", "San Juan Island", "Vashon Island"],
    correctAnswer: "Bainbridge Island",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Seattlites love their puppies!  There are more dogs in this city, according to the last census data than:",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Cars", "Grocery stores", "Trails"],
    correctAnswer: "Children",
  },

  {
    question:
      "The Emerald City was founded in 1851, and it's oldest neighborhood is",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Beacon Hill", "Greenlake", "Central District"],
    correctAnswer: "Georgetown",
  },

  {question: "Seattle recycles-A LOT. What percentage of the city's waste is recycled annually?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
        "30%",
        "51%",
        "42%"
    ], 
    correctAnswer: "60%"
  },

  {question: "Seattle doesn't really get as much rainfall as many of us locals might think.  In fact, Seattle ranks _____ in average rainfall in America!",
    incorrectAnswers: [
        "51st",
        "17th", 
        "5th",
],
correctAnswer: "32nd"

  },
];
